{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "Compared to the others Mark is ___.",
      "a": "more diligent student",
      "b": "the more diligent student",
      "c": "the most diligent student",
      "d": "the most diligent student of all",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Superlative form: Used when three or more things are being compared \n- Structure: The +adj +est (One syllable word) ; the most + adj (Two-syllable words)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "She feels ___ when she is cooking.",
      "a": "the happiest",
      "b": "happiest",
      "c": "the happier",
      "d": "happily",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Superlative form: Used when three or more things are being compared \n+ Structure: The +adj +est (One syllable word) ; the most+ adj (Two-syllable words) \n- happy -&gt; happiest ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Everyone has a right to enjoy his liberty, and his ___ life.",
      "a": "much more",
      "b": "much less",
      "c": "indeed",
      "d": "so",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "-When much is an adverb, it is mainly used before comparative adjectives",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where is Jane? \"I haven't the ___ idea.\"",
      "a": "better",
      "b": "least",
      "c": "little",
      "d": "less",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- I haven't the least idea = I have no idea",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "This is _________ sight I've ever seen.",
      "a": "the beautiful",
      "b": "a more beautiful",
      "c": "the most beautiful",
      "d": "more beautiful",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Superlative form: Used when three or more things are being compared \n+ Structure: The +adj +est (One syllable word) ; the most+ adj (Two-syllable words) ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "When you run, you must go as ___ :",
      "a": "possible as you can",
      "b": "possible as fast",
      "c": "possible fast as you can",
      "d": "fast as possible",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Positive form of adjective: compare that something is equal to some thing \n+ Structure: So....as is used in negative sentences, while as.... as.... is used in affirmative ones",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Johnson has only one sister, but I have ___ eleven brothers and sisters.",
      "a": "no more than",
      "b": "not more than",
      "c": "no less than",
      "d": "not less than",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- No less than = at least",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "___ man in the world does not know everything.",
      "a": "The wise",
      "b": "Wise",
      "c": "Wisest",
      "d": "The wisest",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Superlative form: Used when three or more things are being compared \n+ Structure: The +adj +est (One syllable word) ; the most+ adj (Two-syllable words) \n- wise -&gt; wisest ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "He is so idle. He is ___ man to succeed in the attempt.",
      "a": "the last",
      "b": "a last",
      "c": "the later",
      "d": "a later",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- The last= final",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "They were ___ content that it should be like that.",
      "a": "more",
      "b": "better",
      "c": "more than",
      "d": "less",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- The comparative form: Used when two objects or persons are being compared \n- Structure: Adj (One syllable word) + er than; More + adj (Two-syllable words) + than",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "39",
      "subcategorylv2": "4",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}